rapid4search.com 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy | eBook Search Engine and Price Comparison | Leatherbound

This privacy policy sets out how LeatherBound(Leatherbound.me) uses and protects any information that you give LeatherBound when you use this website.

LeatherBound is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

LeatherBound may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 24th Jan 2013. 

We collect information from you when you register on our site or subscribe to our newsletter. 

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy..

Like millions of other websites, Leatherbound is using analytics(such as Google Analytics) tools.

The following information may be collected for analytics:

What website you came from to get here.

How long you stay for.

What kind of computer you’re using.

And quite a bit more.

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

1)To personalize your experience  
(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)

2)To improve our website  
(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)

3)To send periodic emails  
The email address you provide for registration, may be used to send you information and updates of our services, in addition to receiving occasional website news, updates, related product or service information, etc.  
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to keep track of advertisements and analytics information.

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Leatherbound includes third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
